Lewes mixed that ingredient himself
He never lets anyone see it
He just grinds it into powder
and hands it to me
I
I don't know
You don't know
And you fucking dared to say
you had the recipe
I pay you 30,000 a month
Just for this secret recipe
You don't know
Yet you dared to take this job
Boss
Give me a little more time
I can definitely figure it out
I secretly watched him mixing
I know all the ingredients
I just need to figure out the ratio
Five days
If you can't figure it out
You're fired
Lewes someone is here for you
Hello boss
I'm from Health Biotech
This is our company's latest
Special frog feed
It helps frogs gain weight fast
Gain 10 grams of meat in 3 days
The effect is very obvious
Thanks
I'll contact you if needed
OK
Here is my business card
Why did you throw it away
Don't we also need to use
Finished feed
From what he said
This feed has a higher growth rate
It contains a lot of hormones
It will make the forest frogs' weight surge
in a short time
But it easily turns female frogs into males
And causes deformities
We absolutely cannot use it
Turn into male frogs
Only female forest frogs are valuable
Will anyone buy such a scam
There are always people who
Take risks for short-term gains